<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on blog etc</title>
    <link>http://iemre.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on blog etc</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 13:58:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://iemre.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Software Development from Apple iPad</title>
      <link>http://iemre.github.io/posts/software-development-from-ipad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 13:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iemre.github.io/posts/software-development-from-ipad/</guid>
      <description>This post describes my current &amp;ldquo;work from iPad&amp;rdquo; set-up. There are a few good reasons for doing this:
Battery. This is a big reason for me to take the iPad with me on the go instead of a laptop. Its battery lasts days. Portability. The iPad is smaller and lighter than most laptops. And I can use it as an e-reader on public transport. Drawing with the Apple pen Hardware The 2018 iPad Pro with 11&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; display, 64GB storage - https://support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Algorithm Journal: Graph Colouring with k=2</title>
      <link>http://iemre.github.io/posts/graph-colouring-with-k-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 12:15:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iemre.github.io/posts/graph-colouring-with-k-2/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re given an array of rivals:
rivals = [&amp;quot;A&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;B&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;C&amp;quot;]
And a list of matches between two rivals represented in tuple form:
matches = [(&amp;quot;A&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;B), (&amp;quot;B&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;C&amp;quot;)]
Assign a label (either &amp;ldquo;good&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;bad&amp;rdquo;) to each rival, so that there is no match where both rivals have the same label.
Initial thoughts on the solution At a first glance, it sounds very similar to the Graph Colouring problem. In fact I believe it is no different from it, although it is a special case of the graph colouring problem with 2 as the number of colours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Review: Jarvis Bamboo Standing Desk</title>
      <link>http://iemre.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 21:58:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iemre.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been pondering whether or not a standing desk would add value to my work flow and life. And I finally got the Jarvis Standing Desk for a couple reasons:
It is probably a good investment now with the coronavirus pandemic and the advent of remote work.
I find that I need to stretch and move my body quite frequently.
Many times during the day, I find that I need to do something quick on my computer and I feel like having to sit down for that is slow and inefficient.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
